DIMITRI LAVRENTEV

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

DETAILS

ADDRESS

Germany

PHONE

+49 015209262435

EMAIL

email@dlavrentev.de

SKILLS

Ability to Work in a Team

Knowledgable in User Interface/ User Experience

Effective Time Management

Adaptability

Fast learning

Leadership Skills

HOBBIES

Kickboxing, Reading, Programming

LANGUAGES

German

• • • • •

English

• • • • 0

Russian

 \bullet \bullet \circ \circ

LINKS

<u>LinkedIn</u>

<u>GitHub</u>

Portfolio Website

PROFILE

I have become a front-end developer with an industrial and mechanical professional background. From this experience I can transfer my knowledge of working in a small team, encounter, and repair machine errors all with precision and responsibility. At mimo_dev I learned the fundamentals of writing dry code, handling and using the developer tools, and most importantly breaking down problems to the essentials. Furthermore I was also able to strengthen my foundation in team collaboration and communication and to plan projects effectively. I am proficient in an assortment of technologies, including HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, React, MySQL, Node.js, and Git.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Machine operator, Daimler AG

Kassel

Sep 2018 — Present

- · Remained flexible, adaptable, and punctual.
- · Remained focused and committed to precise work.
- · Served as a safe and effective machine operator on various large-scale projects.
- · Repaired and found many machine errors in the work process

Apprenticeship as a cutting machine operator, Daimler AG

Kassel

Aug 2015 — Aug 2018

overall grade: 1,4

EDUCATION

Technical diploma, Reichspräsident Friedrich-Ebert-Schule

Fritzlar

Jul 2013 — Jul 2015

overall grade: 1,8

Certificate of Graduation in Web Development, mimo_dev

Nov 2021 — Jun 2022

Covered the fundamentals required for any web developer by learning a stack of the most popular technologies.